(1983年 斯塔顿岛) Barney 我们得说再见了
（ staten island 1983 ) Barney, afraid this is good-bye.
你老妈太唠叨了 说我会把你带坏
Your buzz kill of a ma thinks I'm a... a badinfluence on you.
什么? 那真是... 你教我的那个词怎么说的?
What? That's... What is that word you taught me?
"狗"什么的? (狗屁)
"Bull" something?
不管怎么样 她总是你老妈 而我...
But she's yourmother and I'm...
不过是你的Jerry叔叔 所以我想 这是我们最后一次见面了
you know, I'm justyour Uncle Jerry. So, this is the lasttime I can see you.
可下周说好要带我去看 Zeppelin翻唱乐队的啊
But you're supposed totake me to see that Zeppelin cover bandnext week.
那晚肯定相当...
The night is gonna be...
川及(传奇)
Led-and-Jerry.
抱歉 兄弟 只能这样了  不过千万别忘记教你的东西
Sorry, buddy, but this is it. But don't you forgetyour training.
谁是魔术师最好的朋友?
What's a magician's best friend?
喝醉的观众
A drunk audience.
表现不错
Attaboy.
我们去过的活动徽章还在吗?
You still got that buttonfrom the festival we went to?
合法化! 1983年
legalize???
现在呢 我要把它放在你脑后...
Now... I'm gonna put this right inside your brain,behind your ear...
这样我就知道你不会忘记我了
so that I'll know thatyou won't forget me.
永别了 兄弟
See you, buddy.
嘿
And hey...
派对 永不断
Never... stop... partying.
孩子们 1983年 Barney眼看着 他的爸爸走出他的生命
Kids, in 1983,Barney watched his father walk out of his life.
而2011年 他们父子两人 首次重逢不欢而散...
And in 2011, when theirfirst reunion ended badly...
只要能再参与你的生命 我什么都愿意做
I'd love nothing morethan to be a part of your life.
而这次 是Barney先离开
This time it was Barneywho did the walking.
再见
Bye.
我们以为那就是他们的结局了 不过 几周后...
And that was almostthe end of it. Except, a few weeks later...
我爸气死我了 猜猜今天谁给我打电话了
I am so angry at my dad! Guess who called me today.
快啊 猜猜看
Go on, guess.Mmm.
- 你爸爸? - 我老爸!
- Your dad? - My dad!
- Barney Stinson - 嗨 Barney 是爸爸
- Barney Stinson. - Hi, Barney. It's your dad.
想和我还有JJ一起去钓鱼吗 就周六早上
Look, would youlike to go fishing with me and J.J.on Sunday morning?
等等 我看下我的性格啊
Ooh, hold on, let mecheck my personality.
不去 绝不会去
Oh, no. Turns out I would neverdo that in a million years.
Barney
Barney, look...
我知道 你对爸爸很失望...
I know you're disappointedthat your dad is just...
因为我不过是个 无聊的乡下驾驶教练
a boring old driving instructorfrom the suburbs.
不过过去的我... "疯狂Jerry" ?
But that guy I used to be... "Crazy Jerry"?
他可不是好人 酗酒 彻夜派对 到处睡女人
He was bad news! Drinking, partying,sleeping around.
不可能永远糜烂下去
The party can't go on forever.
你现在35岁了 我想你也开始意识到了 对吗
You're 35; I'm-I'm sureyou're starting to realize that, right?
你真是太对了
You do not knowhow right you are.
对个屁
Zero right!
我们还没有老到干不了事的地步
We're not getting too old for anything.
你确定? 我怎么觉得每年至少一次 我们会觉得自己太老了
You sure? I feel like we collectivelylearn the opposite lesson, like, at least once a year.
我不得不接受这丑陋的真相
I have to face an ugly truth.
Jerry Whittaker 我的亲生爸爸
Jerry Whittaker, my own father,
可真是一点都不帅
is anti-awesome-etic.
我知道 疯狂Jerry肯定还在
I know. Crazy Jerry's stillin there somewhere,
只不过是被20年来修草坪
but he's trapped under 20 yearsof lawnmower parties
和拼车烧烤给困住了
and carpool barbecues.
哇 你对郊区还真是不了解
Wow, you know nothingabout the suburbs.
这周六晚 我要把疯狂的他释放出来
Well, this Saturday night, I am bustin' him out.
我要让Jerry知道 他不该放弃原来的生活
I'm gonna
make Jerry realize he was wrong about giving up his old life
我要让他过一个永生难忘的夜晚
by showing him the awesomest nightof all time.
既然是永生难忘的夜晚
And for the awesomest night of all time,
我需要一群永生难忘的朋友来配合
I'm going to needthe wesomest friends of all time,
好了 我都认识些谁呢?
Okay, who do I know?
各位...
Guys...!
你们有谁认识乔治克鲁尼?
Do any of you knowGeorge Clooney?
好了 我爸爸快到了 今晚我要一切尽可能完美
Okay, my dad's almost here. I need everything to be as awesome as possible tonight.
- 所以... - 所以你才把我们叫到这来嘛
- That's...  - why youbrought these guys.
不 所以我才叫这些人来
No. That's whyI brought these guys.
我对你们的身份做了点小小的改动
I've made some minor improvementsto your identities.
看了卡片就知道
- Uh. - Mm! - You'll find themon these cards.
- 改动? - 是啊 老兄
- Improvements?!- Yeah. Bro,
我们四个已经是最完美...
we are already the four jiggity-jamminest dudesand dudettes this side of...
好吧 还是看卡片吧
Okay, let's see the cards.
Robin 除非是车追露乳美女的新闻 否则没人会看
Robin, no one watches the news unless it's a car chaseor a nip slip.
你现在的身份是专业品酒师
You are now a professional scotch taster.
Lily Jerry需要明白的是 有些生活方式不比一夫一妻差
Mm!
Lily, Jerry needs to learnthat other lifestyles are just as fulfillingas monogamy,
所以你和Marshall现在是开放婚姻
so now you and Marshallare in an open marriage.
恶心!
- Whoo-hoo! - Gross!
还有 Marshall 不能说你失业了
Also, Marshall, you can't just be unemployed,
你现在是严重酗酒 沉溺女色的剧作家
so you are now a gin-swilling, womanizing playwright.
Ted 你就做你自己
And, Ted, just be yourself.
怎么可能
Just kidding.
这里是一堆你绝对要避免的话题
Here's a giant pile of topicsyou should avoid talking about.
好吧 这肯定会很有趣
Well. Well, this couldactually be fun.
事实上 我想Oscar Wilde曾说过
In fact, I believe itwas Oscar Wilde who said,
"一个人最不诚实的时候 是他在谈论..."
"Man is least himselfwhen he talks..."
- Ted 看卡片 - 啊 好的
- Ted, card. - Ah. You're right...
"不准引用Oscar Wilde的话"
"No quoting Oscar Wilde."
最后一点 Robin 你和Ted是一对
Finally... Robin, you're dating Ted.
啊 天 为什么啊?
Aw, man! Why?
我身边不能有单身女性朋友
I can't have any single female friendslying around.
我爸爸肯定会一直说 "你为什么不娶Robin?"
My dad'll be all,"Why don't you marry Robin?
"你们俩很般配 其实你自己知道  你和她在一起是最快乐的"
"You guys are cute together.Deep down, you know you were never happierthan when you were with her."
不用了 谢谢
- Uh... - no, thanks.
嘿 Barney 爱死我的新身份了 不过有个小问题...
Hey, Barney... lovethe new identities. Little thing...
我不想当裸体的超级忍者
instead ofbeing a naked super ninja,
我想当"穿Prada的恶魔"里的 Meryl Streep
can I be Meryl Streepin The Devil Wears Prada?
那电影太棒了
- How good was that movie?
- 太好看了 - 哦 天哪
- ??? - Oh, my God.
还有...
- ??? - And...
所以要给你们新身份了
hence new identities.
Barney的爸爸总算来了
And so Barney'sdad finally showed up.
Jerry 还记得Marshall吧 他是位知名作家
Jerry, you remember Marshall... he's a well-known writer.
剧作家 我们都是作家 只是有些人还不知道怎么写
Playwright.We're all writers, just some of us don't knowwhat our story is yet.
Lily 他的妻子
Lily, his wife.
大部分晚上是
Well, most nights.
我可不想让戒指 影响我们的幸福时光
Mama don't let no ring get in the way of a good time.
那... 有点郁闷
That's... a little depressing.
嗨
- Uh, - hi again.
我是Ted Jerry 你还记得我的女朋友吧
Ted. Oh, and, Jerry, you remember my girlfriend.
我是Robin 嗨 很高兴再次见到你
Robin. Hi.So nice to see you again.
等等 Jerry 我还是告诉你真相吧
Wait, wait. Jerry, I got to tell you the truth.
各位 我还是告诉他吧
Guys, I'm gonna tell him.
我们几个组成了一个乐队
We're also a band.
2 3 4
Two, three, four!
老爸老妈浪漫史 第六季第21集
how i met your mother s06e21
-==http://www.1000fr.net==- 謦灵风软影视论坛荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业用途
www.1000fr.net presents
-=风软FRM字幕组=- 翻译: warmcherry evelynjiao 校对: evelynjiao 时间轴:小翁同学
Capture:ID@FRM Sync:小翁同学@FRS
Ow! Yeah!
周六晚上了 该放松下了 对吧?
So, Saturday night... time to cut loose, right?
有人想分瓶啤酒吗?
Who wants to split a beer?
我们不在这喝 今晚我们要好好疯一下
we're not drinking here. Tonight we're going big.
想一下 应该先去哪个酒吧呢?
Let's see, what clubshould we hit first?
"曾经" "错误"...
There's Club Was,there's Wrong...
额 这些酒吧早就关门了
Um, those places shut downa long time ago.
- 哦 不 - "哦 不" 也关门了
- Oh, no. - Oh, No shut down, too.
- "哪里"呢? - "哪里"在哪里?
- There's Where? - Where's Where?
"曾经"就在"哪里"不是吗?
Where's where Waswas, isn't it?
不 "曾经"以前不是在"哪里"的  而是在"错误"对吗?
No, Was wasn't where Where was, Was was where Wrong was, right?
- 好吧 - 不去 "好吧"那地方逊毙了
- Okay. - Not Okay.That place is lame.
"好吧"逊毙了? 我还以为 那是个同志酒吧 难道是"错误"?
Okay is Lame?I thought Lame was a gay bar. Or is that Wrong?
不对 不是"错误"
That's wrong.That's not Wrong.
- 各位 集中点 - 哦 我喜欢"集中"我们去那吧
- Guys, focus. - Oh, I like Focus.Let's go there.
- 哪里?  - 不去"哪里" 去"集中"
- Where? - Not Where. Focus.
我还以为"集中"已经关门了
I thought Focus was closed.
没有 "曾经"关门后再开业 改名为"关门"了
No, Was was Closed. Once Was shut down,it reopened as Closed.
- 所以"关门"还开着 - 不是 "关门"也关了
- So Closed is open. - No, Closed is closed.
我不知道 去"第三基地"怎么样?
I don't know. Third base! Right?
不要 那里都是些兄弟会的人
Ew, Third Baseis all frat guys.
随便去哪 好吧?
I'll go anyplace, okay?
不去 "好吧"那逊毙了
Not Okay. Okay is lame.
"好吧"可不逊 "逊毙了"是个同志酒吧
Okay is not Lame. Lame is a gay bar.
- 各位 闭嘴 - 不 "闭嘴"也关门了
- Guys, shut up. - No, Shut up shut down.
真不敢相信 我现在对酒吧这么不熟悉
I can't believe I don't knowthe clubs anymore.
各位 就随便选一个啊 好吧?
Guys, just pick a club, okay?
不去"好吧"
Not Okay!
"好吧"逊毙了 是个同志酒吧
Okay is Lame! Gay bar.
其实 我曾偶然去过一次
For the record, I wasin there once by accident.
我很确定 其实正确读音是Lama
I'm pretty sure it'spronounced Lam茅.
没希望了 是不是?
It's hopeless, isn't it?
哇
Wow.
这里的女生都可以当我们女儿了
A lot of these girlsare young enough to be our daughters.
我知道 老爹回来了
I know. Daddy's home.
爷爷也回来了 今晚太震撼了
And Granddaddy's home! Tonight rocks so hard!
我可能对这个图章过敏
I might be allergicto this stamp.
天哪 我暗恋的人在这
Oh, my God,my secret crush is here.
Mila Kunis?!
不是 是我暗恋的人
No, my secret crush.
我们是几年前遇到的
We met a few years ago.
嗨 我想征求下女士的意见
Hi. I could usea woman's opinion.
我穿这件怎么样?
Is this working for me?
额 不太搭
Uh... no.
这件衬衫难看的唯一好处
The only good thing about how ugly that shirt is,
就是让人们忽略它多么不适合你
is that it distractsfrom how terribly it fits you.
我试的是裤子
I was trying on the pants.
哦
Oh.
话没说完 我就走了 所以我们也没后续
I had to leave before we could finish talking, so that was it.
从那之后 我就...
You know, eversince then, I've always...
天哪 他过来了
Oh, my God,he's coming over here.
- 你好 - 嗨
- Oh. Hello. Hi. - Hi.
几年前在商店... 你实在让我有点尴尬
A few years ago ata department store... ...did you embarrassthe hell out of me?
不好意思 是你的衬衫实在太丑
Oh, I'm sorry,you must have me confused with the shirtyou were wearing that day.
我很幸运啊
I should be so lucky.
嗨 我是Ted
Hi! I'm Ted!
Robin的男朋友 很高兴见到你
Robin's boyfriend! Nice to meet you.
好吧 额...
Right. Um...
很高兴再见到你
it was really niceto see you again.
我也是
- Mm-hmm. You, too.- Yeah.
你欠我个人情
You owe me one.
这地方不错吧?
Man, isn't this place great?
难说 太吵了
Uh, I don't know.It's so loud!
典型的资产阶级
And so bourgeois.
我的很多剧本都是关于资产阶级
Many of plays areabout the bourgeois.
还有厌倦的
And ennui.
有一部摇滚音乐剧是关于...
And one rock opera about...
一家冰冻酸奶店
a frozen yogurt shop.
Lily 说说你们的开放婚姻吧
Uh, L-Lily, uh, talkabout your open marriage.
结束了一整天的会议
Okay. Well, after a long dayof style meetings
拍照
and photo shoots
还有一整天为难我的助理之后
and being way too mean to my assistant,
我有时候会和内衣模特上个床
I sometimes bangan underwear model.
- 我的天哪 - 我也四处风流
- My goodness! - I sleep around, too.
和她差不多 甚至有过之而无不及
Just as much. A little more, even.
那也只是因为你整天没别的事干
Oh, uh, only 'cause youhave nothing to do all day.
我们又要开始吵架了吗 写剧本是个实在的活
Are we having this fight again? Writing plays is a real job!
我一周工作90小时 就是为了补贴你"实在的活"
I work 90 hours a weeksubsidizing your "real job."
我获得了Tony奖!
I won a Tony!
我把法式烹饪带到了美国
I brought French cookingto America!
- 什么? - 我们喝酒吧
- What? - Let's do shots.
不 谢谢 Barney 我明早还要和JJ去钓鱼
Uh, no, thank you, Barney. I have that fishingtrip with J.J. early tomorrow.
我 我还是少喝点好
I... I better take it easy.
别啊 难道你不记得 小时候和我说的话了吗?
No. Don't you remember what you saidto me when I was a kid?
"派对永不断"
"Never stop partying."
我说过吗 对一个6岁的孩子?
I said that? To a six-year-old?
我不记得了
I don't remember that.
你不记得你对我说过的 最后一句话了?
You don't rememberthe last thing you said to me when I was a kid?
你还是回家吧
Well... you know, why don't youjust go back home?
但我想和你出来玩啊
But I want to hang out with you.
没错 不过我只想和疯狂Jerry玩 而不是宅老头Jerome
Yeah, well, I want to hang outwith Crazy Jerry, not Stay-at-Home Jerome.
好吧
Fine.
你们想和疯狂Jerry玩?
You want Crazy Jerry?
好了 他来了
There! You got him!
不好意思 酒劲要过几分钟才上来
I apologize... it might takea few minutes to kick in.
- Oh... - Oh... - ??
嘿 小甜心 拿五杯啤酒过来
Hey, sugar!Five beers for the table,
给我一杯"七七" (鸡尾酒名) 把你的电话号码告诉这个人吧
a Seven-and-Seven for me, and your ten digitsfor this guy here!
今晚疯狂Jerry要燃烧这家舞厅
Tonight Crazy Jerry'sgonna burn this disco down!
Whoo! Wa-hah!
你们相信吗 这太棒了
Can you believe it? This is awesome!
Barney 这哪里棒了?
Barney, how is that awesome?
我终于知道被老爸宓 是什么感觉了
I finally know what it's liketo be embarrassed by my dad.
你真的以为如果我们是开放婚姻
So you really believe that if we were inan open marriage
你会胜过我?
that you would do better than me?
嘿 你在很多事情上都胜过我
Hey, you do better than meat a lot of other things,
比如消化乳制品 还有拿东西
like digesting dairy... and reaching for stuff.
你知道吗 游戏开始
Okay, you know what? Game on.
如果我比你先拿到五个电话号码
If I can score fivenumbers before you can,
那我们就在卫生间嘿咻 不过...
then we have sexin the bathroom. But...
如果你比我先拿到五个电话号码
if you can scorefive numbers before me,
那我们还是在卫生间嘿咻
then we have sexin the bathroom.
那就是我们通常的赌注喽
So our usual wager.
成交
Deal.
嘿 呃 Jerry
Hey, uh, hey, Jerry,
你...你要不要回来坐?
y... you really want to beout here like this?
不好意思 你这个老古董 跳舞违法了吗
Oh, sorry, small-town preacherfrom the Midwest, is there a law against dancing?
不 当然不是 我只是...
No, of course not.I... I just...
这家俱乐部太逊了
Oh, this club blows.
我们去世上最棒的派对吧 去纽约的大街上!
Let's hit the greatestparty in the world, the streets of New York!
好 我们去吧
- Yeah! Let's do it!- Yeah!
呃 先把领带弄好吧 不过重要的还是派对!
Uh, maybe fix the tie. But mostly, party!
好了 Jerry走了 咱们分手
Okay, Jerry's gone;Let's break up.
好吧 "我愿意为你偷一整个乐队" 结束了 你急什么?
Okay. "I would have stolenyou a whole orchestra." There. What's the rush?
刚刚和我说话的那个 以为我们在交往的男人
Well, that guy who came over herewho thinks we're dating,
我有点喜欢他 你能帮我澄清吗
I kind of have a crush on him. Can you help me clear it up?
什么 那个男的? 他只能打4分
Really? That guy? He was, like, a four.
4分? 天啊 你太没眼光了
A four? God, you are, like, the worst judge of guys ever.
如果他是4分 那你几分?
Okay, if he is afour, what are you?
我并不完美 我有8分...
Hey! I'm not perfect;I'm an eight...
半
and a half.
你是负零点五分吧
You're a doofus and a half.
好吧 我们去跟他说吧 你在哪儿认识这个猥琐男的?
Fine. Let's go talk to him. Where'd you meetthis booger-eater anyway?
在Dawes的清仓大甩卖上
At a close-out sale at Dawes.
真的吗
- Really? - ??
我记得那次大甩卖
I remember that sale.
嘿 Robin
Hey, Robin.
哦 Ted 不
Oh, Ted. Oh, no.
看我买了什么
Look what I just bought.
好看吧 好看吧?
Right? Right?
等等 我们那时候在交往
Hold on.We were dating then.
我清楚的记得 因为那晚我们干柴烈火非常激情
I specifically remember, because we had greatsex that night.
非常激情
Great sex.
让我猜猜 有人喜欢...
Let me guess. Someone wants to knock...
靴子
boots.
Boots.
快把衣服脱了
Just take off your damn shirt.
好了
Okay.
好的
All right.
好的 停
All right. Whoa, stop.
- 什么? - 停 非常好
- What? - Stop. Perfect.
可是我... 我看不见了 你也看不见我
But I... I can't see,and you can't see me.
是的 这样很好
Yeah. Yeah, just like that.
你在想象那个男的!
You were picturing your crush!
总得有人这么做啊
Well, somebody had to.
好吧 好吧 回答我
Okay, okay, answer me this.
你确定一定以及肯定...
Are you absolutely sureit had nothing whatsoever...
这和靴子没关系吗?
to do with the boots?
是的
Yes.
听到了吗 大伙 她说"愿意" 我们要结婚了!
You hear that, everybody? She said "yes"!We're getting married!
我爱她 我永远不会让她离开
I love this girl. I'm never letting her go.
嘿 干杯 朋友
Hey... Bottoms up, amigo!
在这之后 Barney的记忆有些模糊
After that, Barney's memory of the nightgot a little hazy.
你想打我吗?
You want to fight me?
跟我打啊 白痴
Well, I'll fight you, dummy!
你都不知道!
You don't even know!
嘿 嘿 看我的
Hey, hey! There we go! ????
看我从地上拔出了什么!
Oh, look what I just rippedout of the ground!
Oh...!
我刚刚吐在了...
I just puked on thehood of that...
那辆警车上!
police car!
真遗憾 你那个朋友 是剧作家而不是律师
Too bad your playwright friend isn't a lawyer.
Barney 对不起
Barney, I'm so sorry.
和疯狂Jerry出来就会变成这样
I'm afraid thisis what it's like hanging out with Crazy Jerry.
没事的 老爸
It's okay, Dad.
我没想到今晚会这么精彩
I never thought tonightwould be so awesome!
那么... 下一站去脱衣舞俱乐部吧
So... next stop, strip club.
- "活力豹"有特别的... - 天啊 Barney 我没醉!
- The Lusty Leopardhas a special... - Oh, for corn's sake,Barney, I'm not drunk!
- 什么? - 我告诉过你我已经从良了
- What? - I told you,I don't party anymore,
可是你不愿接受这个答案
and you wouldn't takeno for an answer.
所以...
So...
我用了一点小把戏...
I used a little...sleight-of-hand...
迷惑你的视线
to make you think otherwise.
给你
- Here you go. - Whoa!
干杯 朋友!
Bottoms up, amigo!
Mm.
可你做了那么多疯狂的事
But all thosecrazy things you did.
你记不记得 一个魔术师最好的朋友是谁?
Do you happen to rememberwhat a magician's best friend is?
喝醉的观众
A drunk audience.
你想打我吗?
You want to fight me?
打我啊 白痴!
Well, I'll fight you, dummy!
不 不 不
No, no, no.
你都不知道 就在这儿!
You don't even know! Right here!
看
Look.
看我从地上扯出了什么!
Look what I justripped out of the ground!
Oh...!
怎么了?
What just happened?
我... 我刚刚吐在了...
I... I just pukedon the hood of that...
那辆警车上
police car.
你为什么要这么做?
Well, why do all those things?
我以为如果我向你展示...
I figured ifI showed you what...
"派对永不断"是什么样子
"never stop partying"really looked like,
你就会明白自己不可能永远这样
you'd realize you can't do it forever.
算了
Oh, well.
你一整晚都对我撒谎 就为了你自私的理由?
You lied to me all nightfor your own selfish reasons?
老爸...!
Daddy...!
我想和你一起出来 你是我儿子
I wanted to hang outwith you... you're my son.
既然你不愿意我和还有JJ去钓鱼
And since you didn't wantto come with me and J.J. On that fishing tri...
钓鱼
Fishing trip.
我没办法准时赶回去了
I'll never make itback in time now.
你知道 像你这样出色的魔术师 可能知道怎样...
Hey, you know, a... a prettygood magician like you probably knows how to,
比如说 解开一副标准的手铐
say, get out of a standardset of handcuffs.
也许吧
Perhaps.
你不知道的是...
Well, here's somethingyou didn't know...
我也是个不错的魔术师
I'm a pretty goodmagician, too.
阿布拉卡达布拉
Abracadabra!
恭喜你
Congratulations!
谢谢你 好开心啊 我们计划在6月举行婚礼
Oh, hey!Thank you so much. We're super excited.We're thinking June.
好的
Yeah, okay.
好了 混蛋...
Okay, jerk...
你记得你为什么 会买那双红色牛仔靴的吗
do you remember how you ended upbuying those red cowboy boots?
哇
Wow.
OK镇的瑕疵货
Wardrobe malfunctionat the O.K. Corral!
哪个头脑正常的人会...
I mean, who in theirright mind would ever...
你穿那双会很帅的
You would lookso totally hot in those.
有11码的吗?
Do you have these in a size 11?
从神坛上下来吧 你也不是什么圣人
So get off the fieldat the Superdome, because you ain't no saint.
你好 我 呃...
- Hello. I, uh... - Oh.
嗨 Robin
Hi, Robin.
能把你的电话号码给我吗?
Could I have your phone number?
- 我们要找个地方藏起来 - 哪里?
- We need someplace to hide. - Where?
不 Jerry 现在可不是去俱乐部的时候!
No, Jerry, this is not the timeto go to another club!
我们要把你准时送回家去钓鱼
We've got to get you backhome in time for that trip.
可是现在已经没地铁了 出租车也叫不到
But there's no more trains, there's no cabs.
Well, uh...
我在附近有几个驾校的学生
I do have a few drivingstudents in the city.
- 踩油门! Jerry... - 别踩油门
- Step on it! Jerry... - Do not step on it.
- Jerry 我们必须把你准时送回去 - 法律是用来保护...
- Jerry, we have gotto get you home in time for that fishing trip. - The laws are thereto protect...
- 没空管法律了! - 系上安全带 Barney
- This is no time for laws! - Buckle up, Barney.
- 我不会系安全带的 - 我是你爸 你必须听我的!
- I am not going to buckle up! - I am your father! You will listen to me!
嘿 开放婚姻怎么样了?
Hey! How's theopen marriage going?
谁先拿到五个号码了?
Who was the first oneto get the five numbers?
我赢了 我的奖励是... 在卫生间嘿咻
I won that race. My prize...sex in the bathroom.
我如愿以偿了
And I won that race.
真遗憾 那个一见钟情的男人 和你错过了
Aw, sorry that secret crushdidn't work out for you.
没事 我想这是命中注定的吧
Oh, it's okay. I guessit just wasn't meant to be.
你笑什么?
Why are you smiling?
不知道
I don't know.
晚安
Good night.
我又看到那个女生了
Saw that girl again.
你猜怎么着? 她订婚了
And guess what?She's engaged.
所以到此为止了
So that's the end of that.
事情还没结束 还有后续呢
It wasn't the end of that. More on that later.
她的未婚夫 只能算是2分
And her fianc茅?The guy's like a two.
你怎么做到的?
How did you do it?
做到什么?
Do what?
你怎么变成现在这样的?
How did you become this?
我喜欢我的生活 但是...
I mean, I love my life, but...
我不确定这样对不对
I'm not sure I likeloving it.
- 当然了 脱衣舞俱乐部... - 你开歪了
- Sure, strip clubs... - You're drifting.
嘿 我在对你说真心话...
Hey, I'm trying toopen up to you...
不 Perkins女士 你开歪了!
No, Mrs. Perkins,you're drifting!
继续 Barney
Go on, Barney.
每次我想要寻求新的人生 我看看自己的生活
When I think about going foranything more than that, I look at my life,
看看自己 然后...
and who I am, and...
我已经偏离太远了
I'm too far gone.
我已经完了
I'm broken.
儿子 我以前比你还要无可救药
Son, I was far more brokenthan you'll ever be.
看看现在的我
And look at me now.
别误会 要安定下来...
Don't get me wrong... settling down is...
的确是一个挑战 是人生中最大的挑战
a challenge. It's the biggestchallenge of your life.
那你是怎么做到的?
So how do you do it?
魔术师永远不会暴露他的手法
A magician never revealshis greatest trick.
但我给你个提示吧
But I'll give you a hint.
你要遇到命中注定的那个女孩
You gotta meet the right girl.
谁知道呢
Who knows?
也许你明天就会遇见她
Maybe you'll meet her tomorrow.
也许我已经遇到她了
Maybe I've met her already.
停车 手刹
And park.And emergency brake.
我今晚过得很开心
I did have a good time tonight.
如果你想去钓鱼 我们船上还有位子
And hey, if you want to go fishing, we got room in the boat.
下次再说吧
Maybe some other time.
好的
Okay.
还有 呃...
Oh, and, uh...
谢谢你一直保存着这个
thanks for taking suchgood care of this.
这对我来说意义重大
It means a lot to me that youkept it safe all these years.
我要和老爸去钓鱼
I'm going fishing with my dad.
这个...
This...
逊毙了
sucks.
FRS急需时间轴人员 招聘群号：37304379 与最新美剧亲密接触 享受海量FTP下载
Join our FRS and have fun! QQ Group No. 37304379
FRM翻译组招聘邮箱：frzhaopin2@gmail.com 与最新美剧亲密接触 享受海量FTP下载
Join our FRM and have fun frzhaopin2@gmail.com
风软FRM字幕组作品 -==http://www.1000fr.net==- 欢迎加入
welcome to www.1000fr.net